over the edge. Feel like I'm floating
through the
air. The pain I felt is paid for. All is
said and done.
Oh, I am restricted, fixed upon the web.
I need to kick the habit that my mind is
breathing
in. Break it. I've got to break it. I've
got spent all my life holding all of it
closely. I played it in a sense. A feel
of discontent. I'm finally facing it all
fearless.
Feel
it burning the bridge that keeps
us. I'm here and I'm
feeling
fearless. Exaggerated. That's what you
assume. The story is over now. I must
conclude. I ain't conf watching where I
step. Still hanging in the balance. Not
the life I want to live. I will take it
all. Standing tall way the first you
are. Oh oh
oh break out. I've got to see. Break
out. I've got to see. Spend all my life
holding it all closely.
I'm playing it innocent. I feel a
discontent. I'm finally facing it all.
Fearless.
Feelless.
Feelless. Is that a banana?
Hey there everyone. Hope you enjoyed the
music video. Remember to like, comment,
and subscribe. And let me know down
below in the comments what song you want
me to cover next. And if you like what I
do, why don't you support me on Patreon?
And for those who go in there after me,
sorry.